William Santosa

Santa Cruz, CA 95060 | (925) 208-8791 | williamwsantosa@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/williamsantosa

SUMMARY

Second-year student with Junior standing majoring in Computer Science at University of California, Santa Cruz with the Dean's Honor throughout all of university (2020 & 2021). Has 10 years of experience in leadership including customer/personal interaction in martial arts, experienced logistical processes at Amazon Warehouse, and organized Science Olympiad at a state level. Is certified with AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner and proficient in Python, Java, C, and AWS services. Has exposure to SAP ABAP, SAP S/4 Hana Cloud solution, C++, and Lua.

EDUCATION

University of California, Santa Cruz

Santa Cruz, CA

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, GPA: 4.00

Expected to graduate in 2023

Awards: Dean's Honor Fall 2020, Winter 2021, Spring 2021, Fall 2021

Coursework: Computer Architecture, Computer Systems, C Programming, Assembly Language, Calculus, Discrete Math, Abstractions, Linear Algebra

WORK EXPERIENCE

University of California, Santa Cruz

Santa Cruz, CA

College Nine Peer Navigator

June 2021 – Dec 2021

- Introduced freshmen to college and gave advice on how to succeed in their first year
- Held office hours for students that needed help with navigating the university or homework
- Graded and gave feedback to students' projects and classwork

Koo's Martial Arts
San Ramon, CA
Instructor & Coach
July 2017 - Aug 2021

• Introduced students to the forms, techniques, and hard-working philosophy of Taekwondo

• Taught students the importance of hard-work, self-study, and discipline

Baskin School of Engineering at UCSC

Online

Aug 2021

Computer Systems & C Programming Reader

Mar 2021 – June 2021

- Helped students with problem solving and difficult concepts such as depth first search and recursion
- Graded and gave feedback to students' projects and classwork

CERTIFICATIONS

Amazon Web Services Online

Amazon Certified Cloud Practitioner

SKILLS

Languages: Python, Java, C

Technologies: AWS, Git, MATLAB, Premiere Pro, Blender, paint.net

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership, Creativity, Flexible, Eager to learn, Problem solving